Garrison Family Papers, 1694-2005 (bulk 1830-1950)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE 1744-1996
  - Letters to the Garrisons
    - Frayer, William 1935-36 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Freeman, Elizabeth 1911 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Fukui, Eiko 1925-41, undated (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Fuller, Lucy Derby and Samuel Richard 1897-1906 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Fyffe, Elizabeth 1909-52, undated (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - Gaines, Mary L. 1926-29 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Galbraith, F.W. 1900-17 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Gale, Philip B. 1940-45, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Gannett, Mary Thorn Lewis 1887-89 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Gardner, Bertram 1896-1912, undated (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Garland, Hamlin, 189?-1904 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Gay
      - Elizabeth Neall 1895 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - S.M. 1896-1900 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - George
      - Henry 1888-97 (Box 119, Folder 9-10)
      - Henry, Jr. 1891-1909, undated (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - Marie M. 1897 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins 1896, 1898 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Goldthwait, Frances and Joel 1939-45, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Golz, Josephundated (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Gorham, Florence 1915-36 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Gould, Elizabeth Porter 1892 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Gowan, Rosa 1889 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Grady, Anna Elizabeth 1928-32, undated (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Graecen, Bertha and Walter 1929-59, undated (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Gray, Maria Freeman 1899-1909 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Greener, Richard 1879 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Gregory, Eugene M. 1925-29 (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Grew, Mary 1859-1889 (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Grierson, Margaret Storrs 1947-70 (Box 120, Folder 1-13)
    - Grierson, Margaret Storrs 1971-97 (Box 120a, Folder 1-4)
    - Grimké
      - Archibald 1900 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Francis J. 1905 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Sarah 1865 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Griscom family 1936-42, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Guerrier, George P. 1899-1905, undated (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Guyot, Yve 1907 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Habicht, Max and Elizabeth 1929-60, undated (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Hadley, Amos I. 1900-41 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Hale
      - Edward Everett 1880-97 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Nancy 1925 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Hall
      - Bolton 1906-33 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      - Edwardundated (Box 121, Folder 12)
      - Edward R. 1885, undated (Box 121, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 1863-72, undated (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Halle, Ann 1936-41 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Halliday, Eliza W. 1900 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Hallowell, Penrose ("Buck") 1897-1946, undated (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Halvorsan, Anne 1940-42, undated (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Hamill, Esther 1935-48, undated (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Hamlin, Charles E. 1893-97 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Harper, Ida Husted 1909 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Hartwell, Fred 1927-28, undated (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Harwood, Mary R. 1934-43 (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - Hastings, John K. 1900-06 (Box 121, Folder 24)
    - Hauser, Elizabeth J. 1906-08, undated (Box 121, Folder 25)
    - Hautermans, Elsa 1936-40, undated (Box 121, Folder 26)
    - Henry, Richard K., Sr. 1938-43 (Box 121, Folder 27)
    - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth 1856-1906 (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - Hill, Leslie Pinckney 1906, undated (Box 121, Folder 29)
    - Hills
      - Katherine 1906-07 (Box 121, Folder 30)
      - William Henry 1882-1915, undated (Box 121, Folder 31-33)
    - Hillyer, Jeanne and Robert 1961-62 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Himes, Joshua V. 1885-90 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Hoar, George Frisbie 1892 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Hobart, Arthur 1881-95, [See also SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES - Osterville -- Miscellaneous] (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Holbrook
      - Arthur "Sandy" and Sue 1925-45, undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Bertha and Arthur T. 1926-45 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Holley, Sallie 1865 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Holmes, Clara 1879 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Holmes, John Haynes 1915-23 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Holt, Byron W. 1899-1924 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Hooker, Isabella Beecher 1870-89 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Hopper, Lue 1854-61 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Hoskin, John and Kate 1855-89, undated (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Houghton, Henry O. 1877-95 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Howard, Harold S. 1928 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Howe, Julia Wardundated (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Howells, William Dean 1899 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Howland, Emily 1896-1908 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Hubbard
      - Hope 1939-43 (Box 122, Folder 19)
      - Joe and Martha 1941-46, undated (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Hughes, Sarah F. 1905-06, undated (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Jackson
      - Annie Belle 1904-09 (Box 122, Folder 22)
      - George 1867 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Jameson, John D. 1953-54 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Jefferson, Joseph 1882-84 (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Johnson
      - Oliver 1858-88 (Box 122, Folder 26)
      - Samuel (?) 1861 (Box 122, Folder 27)
      - Tom L. 1893-1905 (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - Kelsey, Albert Warren 1904-09, undated (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - Kennedy, Mildred 1903-18 (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - Kiefer, Daniel, [See SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Single tax] (Box 122)
    - Kimball, John C. 1879-1905 (Box 122, Folder 31)
    - Kingman, Edith 1899-1959, undated (Box 122, Folder 32-34)
    - Kirkland, John 1929-30 (Box 122, Folder 35)
    - Kline, Effie H. 1906, undated (Box 122, Folder 36)
    - Kyllman, E. 1890-1909 (Box 122, Folder 37)
    - Lambert, Henri, [See SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Free trade -- International Free Trade League -- Correspondence]
    - Lamont, Thomas W. 1932 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Lanier, David 1927-43, undated (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Lanman, Charles R. 1892-1900 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Laugel
      - Auguste 1879-89 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - Elizabeth Batesundated (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Lauriat, Charles E., Jr. 1904-24 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Lee, Amice 1944-61 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Leggett, Joseph 1892-1909 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Leland, Elsa Tudor 1931-34, undated, [See also DePierrefeu, Elsa Tudor] (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Leland, Marine 1955-59, undated (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Lewis, Enoch 1877-97 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Lieber, Hetty Wood 1923 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Lindsey
      - Anne 1898-1915, undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
      - Kenneth 1913-28 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Livermore, Mary 1886-1902 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Lord, W.R. 1889-1906 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Loud, H.B. 1898-1908 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Lovett, Elizabeth Quincy 1925-33, undated (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Lowell, Josephine Shaw 1892-1903 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Lummis, Charles F. 1900-07, undated (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Lupton, Joseph 1876-89 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Lusk, Carolyn, [See Barr, Carolyn "Shorty"]
    - Lutz, Alma 1949 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - McCormick, Katharine Dexter 1947 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - McIlhenny, Barbara 1932-36 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - MacKay, Alexander Murray 1923-33, undated (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - MacKaye, Percy and Marion 1914-43, undated (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - MacKendrick, Alex 1900-34 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - McKenzie, William P. 1906 (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - McKim
      - Charles Follen 1867-1905 (Box 123, Folder 29)
      - Ella Rosamond 1929, undated (Box 123, Folder 30)
      - James Miller 1867-72 (Box 123, Folder 31)
      - Margaret S.undated (Box 123, Folder 32)
      - Sarah A. Speakman 1864-1890, undated (Box 123, Folder 33)
    - McLaren
      - Agnes 1901 (Box 123, Folder 34)
      - Priscilla Bright 1901-02 (Box 123, Folder 35)
    - Madgaoha, Amandi 1924-59, undated (Box 123, Folder 36)
    - Mark, E.L 1909 (Box 123, Folder 37)
    - Marshall, William E. 1915-22 (Box 123, Folder 38)
    - Martineau
      - Jane 1876-1910 (Box 123, Folder 39)
      - R.F. 1877-1905 (Box 123, Folder 40)
    - Marty, J. 1922, undated (Box 123, Folder 41)
    - Masten, Ann 1931 (Box 123, Folder 42)
    - Maury, G. Bonet 1900-07 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Mawson
      - Camie 1907-10 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - Elizabeth 1879-95, undated (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - May
      - Abby W. 1876, undated (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - Adie 1908 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - George E. 1906-25, undated (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - Joseph 1876-1906 (Box 124, Folder 7)
      - Samuel J. 1864 (Box 124, Folder 8)
      - Samuel J., Jr. 1851-99, undated (Box 124, Folder 9)
      - Valentine H. 1931-36 (Box 124, Folder 10)
      - Winifred H. 1926 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Means, Martha 1929-34 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Mendonça, Salvador de 1886-89 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Meriam, Francis J. 1857, undated (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Merrill
      - Edith 1957-58 (Box 124, Folder 15)
      - Walter M. 1950-70 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Milliken, Samuel 1892-1917 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Mills, James E. 1890-1901 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Moore, Rebecca 1879-1905 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Morgan
      - Allen 1935-46 (Box 124, Folder 20)
      - Lillian 1931, undated (Box 124, Folder 21)
      - Morrill, Midge 1926-31 (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Morse
      - Alice and Frank (Boston Bird Book Company) 1937-39 (Box 124, Folder 23)
      - Joseph B. 1880 (Box 124, Folder 24)
      - Lucy Gibbons 1895-1917, undated (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Murphy, Joseph 1915-31 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - Muther, Josephine 1917-47, undated (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Nichol, Elizabeth Pease 1876-94 (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - Norton, Charles Eliot 1896-08 (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Nowell, Sarah J. 1885-1900, undated (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Nunn, Henry 1915-26 (Box 124, Folder 31)
    - O'Brian, Robert L. 1907-19 (Box 124, Folder 32)
    - Olen, Bea 1940-42 (Box 124, Folder 33)
    - Oliver, Benjaminundated (Box 124, Folder 34)
    - Ordway
      - George 1917-48, undated (Box 124, Folder 35)
      - Robert 1916-43, undated (Box 124, Folder 36)
    - Pankhurst
      - Emmeline 1914 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - Sylvia 1912 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Park
      - J. Edgar 1919-46, undated (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - Maud Wood 1907-51 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Parker
      - George Lawrence 1925, 1946 (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - Theodore 1860, undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Parkhurst, William 1896-05 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Parrish
      - Hannah 1933-34, undated (Box 125, Folder 8)
      - Jean 1933-34 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      - Lydia 1937-38, undated (Box 125, Folder 10)
      - Maxfield Jr. 1932-44, undated (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Parton, James 1890 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Peabody, George Foster 1898-1909 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Peacock, Luva and Albert 1929-31 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Pearson, George A. 1880 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Pease, Charles 1907-08 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Peck, Mary Gray 1946-50 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Peirce, Mary E. 1862, 1899 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Perry, Lt. Theodora 1937-45, undated (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Peterson, Roger Tory 1935-40, undated (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Pethick-Lawrence, Emmeline 1909-14 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Pettingill
      - Charles 1918-41, undated (Box 125, Folder 22-23)
      - Zoë 1928-43, undated (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Philbrick, Eliza 1879-85, undated (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Phillips
      - Ann 1860, undated (Box 125, Folder 26)
      - Wendell 1856-77, undated (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Pillsbury
      - Parker 1860-97, undated (Box 125, Folder 28)
      - Sarah H. 1889 (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Pinkham, Henry W. 1920-41 (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - Pitman, Hattie M. 1879-85, undated (Box 125, Folder 31)
    - Plimpton, Theodore 1926 (Box 125, Folder 32)
    - Poor, Florence 1958, undated (Box 125, Folder 33)
    - Post
      - Alice Thatcher 1895-1928 (Box 125, Folder 34)
      - Louis F. 1904-24, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Free trade and tariff reform --Correspondence] (Box 125, Folder 35)
    - Prang, Louis 1894-1916 (Box 125, Folder 36)
    - Pratt, Winifred 1926-47, undated (Box 125, Folder 37)
    - Price, Lucien 1919 (Box 125, Folder 38)
    - Priestman, Anna M. 1879-91 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Pugh, Sarah 1879 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Purvis, Hattie 1856, 1902 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Putnam
      - A.P. 1897-1900 (Box 126, Folder 4)
      - Caroline 1883-1908 (Box 126, Folder 5)
      - Herbert 1898 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Quincy
      - Edmund 1885 (Box 126, Folder 7)
      - Josiah 1893-96 (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - Marguerite "Daisy D" 1900-28, undated (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Randall, Mary 1889-1907, undated (Box 126, Folder 10-11)
    - Ransom, Alice R. 1916-18 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Redmond
      - Harold 1914-17 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - John 1901-18 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Renfrew, Robert 1922-24 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Richardson
      - Anne 1915, 1941-19, undated (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - Ellen 1878-80 (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - Juliet 1935-39 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Robinson
      - Edward 1892-1905 (Box 126, Folder 19-20)
      - Edwin Arlington 1925 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Robson, William 1859-90 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore 1898, 1915 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Rumely, Mary R. 1935-44, undated (Box 126, Folder 24)
    - Russell, Phebe 1930-35 (Box 126, Folder 25)
    - Ryan, William Wade 1915-19 (Box 126, Folder 26)
    - Safford
      - John 1903, undated (Box 126, Folder 27)
      - Tom 1914, undated (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - Sampson, Edward and Eleanor 1939, 1959 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Sanborn, Franklin B. 1882-1905 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Saunders
      - Babette 1929-39, undated (Box 126, Folder 31)
      - Kenneth 1928-29 (Box 126, Folder 32)
      - Sawyer, Agnes Sampson 1959 (Box 126, Folder 32)
    - Sayre
      - Nora 1962-74, undated (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
      - Nora Clemens 1962-63 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Scaife, Roger L. 1917-38 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Scattergood, J. Henry 1917-32 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Schlesinger, Mary 1898-1909, undated (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Scott, J. Winifred 1923 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Sedgwick, Ellery 1911-16 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Severance, Caroline 1883-1911, undated (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Sewall
      - Harriet Winslow 1889, undated (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - Samuel 1881-85, undated (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Shackleton, Lydia 1908, undated (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Shaw
      - Dr. Anna Howard 1897-1913 (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - S. B. 1896-99 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Sheldon, Rosamund 1963-64, undated (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Simmons, Elizabeth 1878-1905, undated (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Simons, E.H. 1908 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Simpson, Joseph 1877-1901 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Sinclair, Upton 1924 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Smalley
      - Evelyn G. 1884-90 (Box 127, Folder 20-21)
      - Phoebe Garnant 1899, undated (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - Smeal, William G. 1889, 1904 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - Smith
      - Francis 1928-29, 1937 (Box 127, Folder 24)
      - Goldwin 1890-1905 (Box 127, Folder 25)
      - Joseph Lindin 1883-95, undated (Box 127, Folder 26)
      - Stedman 1916-20 (Box 127, Folder 27)
      - Stella Bromage 1943-66, 1985, undated (Box 127, Folder 28)
    - Somerset, Isabel 1895 (Box 127, Folder 29)
    - Southwick, Sarah 1885-95 (Box 127, Folder 30)
    - Spence, Catherine 1894-1909, undated (Box 127, Folder 31)
    - Spring, Rebecca 1903-05 (Box 127, Folder 32)
    - Stafford, Wendell Phillips 1917-18 (Box 127, Folder 33)
    - Stantial, Edna Lamprey 1941-59, undated (Box 127, Folder 34)
    - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady 1899-1900, undated (Box 127, Folder 35)
    - Stearns, Guy B. 1922, 1939 (Box 127, Folder 36)
    - Steinthal, Alfred 1867-1906 (Box 127, Folder 37)
    - Steinwedell, Ann 1926-27 (Box 127, Folder 38)
    - Stephens, Frank 1896-1908, undated (Box 127, Folder 39)
    - Stevens, Arthur W. 1905-09, undated (Box 127, Folder 40)
    - Stone, Lucy 1882-88 (Box 127, Folder 41)
    - Storey, Moorfield 1899-1909 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Sturge, Sophia 1890-92, undated (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Sunday, Billy 1916 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Sweezy, Everett 1916-18, undated (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Talbot, Fritz and Beatrice 1900-59, undated (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Tarbell, Ida M. 1906-09 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Taylor
      - Edward R. 1899-1907, undated (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Hyman 1915-47 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Samuel 1919-42 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Terry, Ellenundated (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Thaxter, Celia 1877 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Thayer, C.C. 1879-89 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Thomas
      - Charles Swain 1939-46 (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - Martha B. O. 1894-98 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Thompson
      - Georgeundated (Box 128, Folder 15)
      - Ruth (Brown) 1888-92 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Tolman, Harriet S. 1910-21 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Torrence, Betty ("Buck") 1929 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Trotter, William Monroe 1914-34, undated (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Tuke, Mabel 1911 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Twain, Mark 1901 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Twitchell, Eliza 1894-1922, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Single tax] (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Upton, Harriet Taylor 1905-08 (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Venturi, Emilie A. 1888-90 (Box 128, Folder 24)
    - Von Erdberg, Amy and Eleanor 1960-65, undated (Box 128, Folder 25)
    - Walsh, Walter 1905-07 (Box 128, Folder 26)
    - Warner, Eleanor 1893-1900, undated (Box 128, Folder 27)
    - Washington, Booker T. 1896-1909, undated, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Race - Education-Tuskegee] (Box 128, Folder 28)
    - Waters, Henry F. 1905 (Box 128, Folder 29)
    - Watts, William P. 1897-1947, undated (Box 128, Folder 30)
    - Webb
      - Alfred 1872-1908, undated (Box 128, Folder 31)
      - Deborah 1894-1908 (Box 128, Folder 32)
      - Ruth D. 1869 (Box 128, Folder 33)
    - Weld
      - Agnes 1908-09, undated (Box 128, Folder 34)
      - Theodore Dwight 1860-80, undated (Box 128, Folder 35)
      - Theodore Grimké 1907 (Box 128, Folder 36)
    - Wellington
      - Henry W. 1901-02 (Box 129, Folder 1)
      - Lydia D. 1901-13 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Martha S. 1902-31, undated (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Wentworth, Rita 1928-30 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Weston
      - Anne Warren 1885-89 (Box 129, Folder 5)
      - Caroline 1901, undated (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Whipple, Charles K. 1883-99 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Whitney, Anne 1883-1904, undated (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Wigham, Eliza 1885-98 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Willard, Frances E. 1887-95 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Wing
      - Charlotte 1937-47 (Box 129, Folder 11)
      - Lester 1933-39 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Winslow, Caroline 1924-28 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Winsor, Ellen 1940-49 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Winston, Martha 1929 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Wise
      - C. E. 1904, n..d. (Box 129, Folder 16)
      - Marguerite A. 1900-26, undated (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Wood
      - Caroline Stratton 1861, undated (Box 129, Folder 18)
      - Charles P. 1854-76, undated (Box 129, Folder 19)
      - Frank 1858-60, undated (Box 129, Folder 20)
      - Hetty 1857-60, undated (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Wright, Zilpha 1958-85, undated (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Wyman, Lillie B.Chace 1894-99, undated (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - Yerrington, J.M.W. 1885-89 (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Yeomans
      - Edward 1929-37 (Box 129, Folder 25)
      - Edward Jr. 1929-30 (Box 129, Folder 26)
      - Julia 1928-39, undated (Box 129, Folder 27)
    - Young
      - Francis and Constance 1941-46, undated (Box 129, Folder 28)
      - Mary B. 1941-44 (Box 129, Folder 29)
      - Zakrzewska, Marie E. 1887-98, undated (Box 129, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Emerson, Claire (Tita) Garrison 1916-41 (Box 130, Folder 1)
      - Garrison
        - Agnes 1872-1916 (Box 130, Folder 2)
        - Alice 1947-81 (Box 130, Folder 3)
        - David Lloyd
          - A-Z 1922-51, undated (Box 130, Folder 4-12)
          - Unidentified 1925-85, undated (Box 131, Folder 1-3)
        - Edith Stephenson 1896-67, undated (Box 132, Folder 1-11)
        - Eleanor 1897-1974, undated (Box 133, Folder 1)
        - Ellen Wright
          - Eagleswood school friends 1857-60, undated (Box 133, Folder 2)
          - Miscellaneous 1856-1908 (Box 133, Folder 3)
        - Francis Jackson 1879-1913, undated (Box 133, Folder 4-5)
        - Frank Wright 1952-61 (Box 133, Folder 6)
        - Wendell Phillips. 1880-89, undated (Box 133, Folder 7)
        - William Lloyd (1805) 1845-66, undated (Box 133, Folder 8)
        - William Lloyd (1838), A-P 1856-09, undated (Box 133, Folder 9-22)
        - William Lloyd (1838), Q-W 1875-09, undated (Box 134, Folder 1-4)
        - William Lloyd (1874)
          - A-Z 1897-1958, undated (Box 135, Folder 1-15)
          - Unidentified
            - Anne 1904-37 (Box 135, Folder 1)
            - Miscellaneous 1897-1947, undated (Box 135, Folder 2)
        - William Lloyd (1902) and Jane 1953-55, undated (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Harwood, Faith Garrison 1928 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Villard, Oswald Garrison 1915 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Condolence letters
      - Garrison
        - Ellen Wright Garrison 1931 (Box 136, Folder 6)
        - Francis Jackson 1916 (Box 136, Folder 7)
        - Frank Wright 1961 (Box 136, Folder 8)
        - Helen Benson 1876 (Box 136, Folder 9)
        - William Lloyd (1805)1879 (Box 137, Folder 1-3)
        - William Lloyd (1838)1909 (Box 137, Folder 4-6)
        - William Lloyd (1874)1964 (Box 137, Folder 7-9)
      - Norton, Katherine Garrison 1948 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Stephenson
        - Benjamin T. 1914 (Box 138, Folder 2)
        - Luda Grant 1930 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Wright, Martha Coffin 1875 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Engagement letters: WLG (1874) and Edith Stephenson1900 (Box 138, Folder 5-8)
    - Wedding and engagement letters: WLG (1838) and Ellen Wright1864 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Wedding letters: WLG (1874) and Edith Stephenson1901 (Box 138, Folder 10-12)
    - Birth congratulations: WLG (1874) and Edith Stephenson Garrison
      - William Lloyd 1902 (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Claire 1903 (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - John Bright 1909 (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - David Lloyd 1906 (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Faith 1910 (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Edith Lloyd 1913 (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Unidentifiedundated (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Postcardscirca 1900-95 WLG (1874) and Edith Stephenson Garrison (Box 140)
  - Third party letters
    - Adams, John Quincy to Edmund Quincy 1838 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Ahlborn, Emily to Roger Clark 1918 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Anthony, Susan B. to Elizabeth Cady Stanton 1871 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Bartlett, J.W. to Emma Buffum 1862 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Blackwell, Henry Brown to Susan B. Anthony 1872 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Carret, Sarah W. to "Dear boy" 1895 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Clark, Roger to Lucy 1947 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Clark, Sarah B. to Margaret Storrs Grierson 1968 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Cockerell, Sir Sydney with Irene Earle Dickson 1943-56 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Cram, Mary Wells to Lizzie Simmons 1899-1905 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Douglass, Helen to Elizabeth Cady Stanton 1900 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Dreier, Theodore to Edward Yeomans 1933 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Gilman, Rev. Nicholas to Rev. George Whitefield 1744-45 (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Gilpin, Charles William to Grace Greenwood 1854 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Grew, Mary to Samuel May1865 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Hamlin, Charles E. to Mrs. Keely 1872 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - Hooker, Isabella Beecher
      - Anthony, Susan B. 1872 (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady 1870-71 (Box 141, Folder 18)